you-cubez.com 2019-06-16

# Privacy Policy | You-Cubez.com

This Privacy Policy is applicable to any personal information, which is submitted via the web site located at  
www.you-cubez.com. We hope the following statement will help you understand how You-Cubez.com collects, uses and safeguards the personal information you provide to us on our site. 

##### Data Collection

Whilst using our service at www.you-cubez.com, you may encounter areas in which you are asked to submit User Information, such as our registration form. 

During both registration and logging in, your IP address is stored as part of the login process. 

You may request for your account to be terminated and User Information removed at any time, by contacing us at info@you-cubez.com. 

We will never sell or lease any personal information obtained from customers to third parties unless required to do so by the law.

##### How your data is used

By submitting your User Information, you allow us to hold this information in a secure manner. 

Your User Information, such as, but not limited to your age, gender and country of residency may be used by third party offerwalls to provide relevant surveys in order to maximise your earnings. 

Your e-mail address may be used to send e-mails regarding new website updates and special offers. Such e-mails may include advertising for third party companies/organisations. 

You may unsubscribe from e-mails at any time, by logging in to your account and unsubscribing or by sending an e-mail to info@you-cubez.com with the subject 'UNSUBSCRIBE'.

##### Cookies

Cookies may automatically be used to collect data about your visit as well as maintaining your login session. "Cookies" are small text files that store basic information. You may choose to disable cookies in your browser, but it may affect your visit; such as the ability to login and earn money.

##### Updates

You may update, amend or correct your personal information under the 'Profile' link in your account or you may notify us via the form on the contact page.

##### Contact/Other

If you have questions or comments with regards to this privacy policy, please use the form on the contact page or e-mail us at: info@you-cubez.com.

Any website that you may connect to from You-Cubez is not covered by this Privacy Policy.

We may change this privacy policy from time to time and so therefore, you should check this page regularly.

Last updated 24th May 2018.
